swiftappraisal.com 2015-02-23

# SwiftAppraisal.com | Privacy Policy

### PRIVACY POLICY.

SwiftAppraisal.com is committed to protecting your privacy. The following statement outlines our privacy policy.

**Personally Identifiable Information.**  
We do not collect personally identifiable information (name, address, etc).  
  
**Automatically Collected Information.**  
Some information is automatically received and sometimes collected from you when you visit our site. We receive and collect the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet; the Internet protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using; the browser software you use and your operating system; the date and time you access our site; and the Internet address of the web site from which you linked directly to our site. We use this information to monitor the usage of our site.

**IP addresses.**  
An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the Web. Web servers, the computers that "serve up" Web pages, automatically identify your computer by its IP address.   
We use IP addresses to administer the site. IP addresses are not linked to identifiable information. 

**Cookies.**  
We use cookies for session tracking.

Session cookies are stored in memory and are only available during an active session, in other words, while you are on the web site. Session cookies do not permanently record data and are not stored on your computer's hard drive. Session cookies do not give the web site access to anything else on your system, including any private information about you.    
The use of cookies is an industry standard: you'll find them at most major sites.   
**  
****No Spam.**  
SwiftAppraisal.com maintains a strict "no-spam" policy. 

**A Special Note About Children.**  
Children are not eligible to use our service and we ask that minors (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to us or use the service. 

**External Links.**  
This website contains links to websites not owned or controlled by SwiftAppraisal.com. The operator of this website is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any such third party sites. 

**Changes to This Policy.**  
SwiftAppraisal.com reserves the right to change, modify, add or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice.

Should you have other questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please contact us.
